>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们看看这个例子。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's
look at this example.
我指的是变量老师和
I am referring to the variable teacher and
那我就叫 " 老师 " 了好吗
then I am calling
the otherTeacher function, okay?
大家都看到了吗
Everybody see that?
现在还没有定义 other 老师的功能，所以
Now, the otherTeacher function
hasn't been defined yet, so
" other教师节 " 功能已挂起，可供我们使用。
that otherTeacher function has hoisted,
it's available for us to use.
第 5 行会发生什么 ?
What's going to happen on line 5?
>> 扬声器 2: [INAUDIBLE]。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [INAUDIBLE].
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 如果你只考虑提升，你就有了
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If you're thinking about
this only in terms of hoisting, you have
提醒自己，第 6 行的 var 老师已提升到第 4.5 行。
to remind yourself that the var teacher
from line 6 got hoisted up to line 4.5.
因此，在第 5 行上打印的内容实际上是未定义的。
And therefore what's gonna get printed
on line 5 is actually undefined.
所以这就是为什么即使有几行代码
So that's why even with
the couple of lines of code,
我们可以骗过你如果你不习惯把这个当作两遍
we can trick you if you're not used to
thinking about this as a two pass system.
如果你把它想象成两道通行证系统
If you think about it
as a two pass system,
显然蓝桶里有个 var 老师
obviously there's a var
teacher in the blue bucket.
有个蓝色大理石在老师之前叫老师
There's a blue marble called teacher
before otherTeacher ever has
有机会逃跑
the chance to run.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们来谈谈 var 提升和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's talk about
the difference between var hoisting and
功能提升。
function hoisting.
因为有人会告诉你所有吊装都很糟糕
Because some will tell you
that all hoisting is bad, and
我要告诉你，我认为有些吊重是有用的，有些则没有。
I will tell you that I think some
hoisting is useful and some is not.
在第 3 行的范围内，我将在范围内提前分配变量，然后
On line 3, I am assigning to a variable
earlier in the scope then when
这都是 var 声明的
it's been var declared.
我从未见过一个无条件的人
I have never met a person that
would say unconditionally,
我觉得这是个很棒的编码方式，就这么做。
I think that's a great coding style,
just do that all the time.
几乎所有人都同意这不是一个好主意
Almost universally,
people will agree it's not a great idea.
我只在我的编码中发现了一个例外
I've only ever found one exception in
all of my coding where that is something
我想做的
that I wanted to do.
而且比我们在这里俯冲得更细致
And it's more nuanced than
what we'll dive into here.
几乎是通用的，我不想在先前的范围内分配变量。
Almost universally, I don't want to assign
the variables earlier in a scope than
在我宣布他们的地方
where I've declared them.
因此，我同意大多数人的意见。
So I would agree with the predominant
majority in that case.
这很罕见，但我同意这件事的大多数，好吗 ?
That's pretty rare, but I agree with
the majority in that case, okay?
那第 8 行呢 ?
But what about line 8?
这个代码坏了因为我叫get老师
Is this code so broken because I'm
calling getTeacher even though
功能声明在底部吗
the function declaration's at the bottom?
很多人熟悉，或者可以，或者
Many more people are familiar with,
or okay with, or
该功能提升的感觉舒适，不存在变量的浪费。
feeling comfortable with the function
hoisting than with the variable wasting.
所以我想说这就看情况了
So I would say it kinda depends.
你可能认为功能提升是不好的，但你可能认为是可以的。
You might think that function hoisting
is bad, but you might think is okay.
我认为这不仅是好的，而且对
And I happen to think not only is it okay,
but its extremely useful for
代码可读性。
code readability.
能够将可执行代码放置在顶部非常有用，并且
It's extremely useful to be able to
put the executable code at the top and
底部的功能。
the functions at the bottom.